yeahbaby.com 2010-05-04

# Privacy Policy for YeahBaby.com

YeahBaby, LLC, operator of YeahBaby.com, is committed to making your search for baby names and baby information as pleasant and successful as possible. Maintaining your privacy is part of that commitment. This privacy policy applies to the use by consumers of YeahBaby.Com and governs online data collection and usage by Yeahbaby.com. 

**What information we collect**  
You may browse the YeahBaby.com site without providing any personally identifiable information but if you choose to use some of our products or services, you will be asked to provide certain personal information such as: contact information (like your full name and address), unique identifiers (such as your email address and phone number), and demographic information (like your zip code). 

When using certain tools on our site, you may be asked to provide additional information. Many YeahBaby.com pages contain a feature to email a friend. YeahBaby.com will not at anytime retain a friend's email address. 

In addition to the personal information that you voluntarily provide directly to us, your "Internet Protocol" or IP address, browser type, domain name, access times and referring web site address are also recorded. This information is collected both during registration on a site or in response to specific requests. This data helps us serve you by allowing us to understand how visitors use our services. 

Some of the services available on our site are provided by third parties and sometimes we will give you the opportunity to opt in to offers from third parties not affiliated with us. If you decide to use these services or accept these offers, we may provide, with your consent, your information to the third party. However, you should note this privacy policy does not apply to information you consent to give to third parties (or voluntarily provide to third parties) not affiliated with us. Any information you give to another party is governed by the rules of that party's privacy policy, which may differ from this privacy policy. We are not responsible for information given to or collected by other parties. Please review their privacy policies prior to providing any information to third parties. 

What we do with collected information When you register on our site, we use the information you provide to us to track what kind of activities you conduct on our site, including, for example, the types of content that you have viewed. 

To provide you the best products and services, we often team with business partners. When you indicate that you want to receive a product or service, or contact a person or organization, we share the data needed for you to receive what you have indicated. We take great care to require these business partners agree by contract not to disclose any personal information they may receive. We may contract with third parties to administer our mailing lists or provide retail services. In such event, your personal information may be shared with such third party for the purpose of administering the products, services and programs you have selected. 

We use your email as a unique identifier in our record system, to verify communications from you, and to send you newsletters, promotion offerings or other email that you ask to receive. You will have the option to stop these communications at any time by unsubscribing according to the instructions in the newsletter, promotion or email. We will also use your information to contact you when necessary for administrative purposes related to your account and to communicate with you about changes to the site, our services or this privacy policy. 

We may, at times, produce reports for advertisers containing aggregate information about our users such as demographic, age and online usage information. This allows us to work more closely with advertisers to provide content and offers that are most relevant to our users. We will never include any personal information of our users in these reports. 

We reserve the right to use or disclose any information without notice or consent as needed to satisfy any law, regulation (including our Terms of Use) or legal request; to conduct investigations of consumer complaints or possible breaches of law; to protect the integrity of our site and our property; to protect the safety of our visitors or others; to fulfill your requests; or to cooperate in any legal investigation. 

In developing our business, we might sell certain assets or the company, or parts of it, may be sold, merged or otherwise transferred. In such transactions, your user information, whether personally identifiable or otherwise, may be one of the transferred assets. 

**Use of Cookies**  
Our site uses a technology called "cookies," which are small files that are placed on your computer by our servers stored by your browser to help keep track of your user profile. We use temporary cookies to remember your personal profile for your convenience, to deliver content specific to your needs and interests, and to ensure you don't see the same advertisement repeatedly. We also use cookies to track user trends and improve areas of our sites that our users find valuable. We do not share cookie information with anyone without your permission. 

**Third Party Advertising**  
YeahBaby.com use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

Some third party advertisers may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. 

Some advertisers or third party ad servers may also use their own cookies. We do not have access to this information collected by third parties.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your browser and our web sites are viewable even if you disable the cookie function on your browser. However, if you disable cookies, some advanced and customized features of our site, as well as other web sites, will not be available to you. 

**Third-Party Sites**  
Our site contains links to other sites. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of web sites that you can link to through our site. 

**Changing your personal information**  
YeahBaby.com provides you the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from our partners and us. To remove your personal information, you can unsubscribe in accordance with the instructions in any communication sent to you. 

**Security of your personal information**  
All YeahBaby.com employees are made aware of its privacy practices through periodic communications and training. We limit access to private and confidential data only to those employees with a specific need to retrieve this information. The personal data we do store on our system is protected by firewall and password. 

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose information online (whether through our services or any other service available online), personal or otherwise, that information can be collected and used by others. For example, if you use chat, forums, bulletin boards, your e-mail or if you post personal information online, you may receive unsolicited messages from others. We have no control over this use of your personal information. 

**Changes To Our Privacy Policy**  
We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy as necessary to maintain the highest protection for our users and to comply with a changing environment. We recommend that you check the policy when you visit our site to be sure you are aware of and understand our current policy. If we make material changes to this policy or in how we will use or collect your personally identifiable information, we will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. 

**Contact Information**  
If you have questions or concerns about our privacy policy or if at any time you feel that YeahBaby.Com has not adhered to this policy, send a message through the "Contact Us" feature of YeahBaby.Com and we'll do our best to determine any problem and quickly respond.
